You have the genital ridge which is influenced by the migration of gonocytes
生殖堤は、卵黄嚢から移動してきた生殖細胞の影響を受けています。
which comes from the vitelline vesicle
卵黄嚢から来た生殖細胞の移動によって影響を受けます。
which will thicken this posterior coelomic epithelium and form what we will call
それは後方の体腔上皮を厚くし、私たちが呼ぶものを形成します。
the anlage of your gonad.
あなたの生殖腺の原基。
The tissue here is a tissue that is swollen by
ここにある組織は、
the migration of gonocytes from the vitelline vesicle.
卵黄嚢から来た生殖細胞の移動によって膨らんだ組織です。
Gonocytes arrive on this epithelial tissue and proliferate.
生殖細胞はこの上皮組織に到達し、増殖します。
proliferate, swell this gonadal tissue and it becomes the genital ridge,
増殖し、この生殖腺組織を膨らませ、生殖堤となります。
genital ridge,
生殖堤、
future ovary or future testicle.
将来の卵巣または将来の精巣。
I have this connection that occurs at the level of the genital ridge.
この結合は生殖堤のレベルで起こります。
Wolffian duct, it was already formed from the pronephros, then it disappeared.
ウォルフ管は、前腎からすでに形成されていましたが、その後消失しました。
It's a collecting duct.
それは集合管です。
The movement here which is pushed laterally, we don't see the adrenal gland here,
ここで側方に押し出されている動きは、ここでは副腎は見えませんが、
but which is pushed here, comes.
しかし、ここで押し出されているのは、
to lead to the creation of a small canal called the Müllerian duct.
ミュラー管と呼ばれる小さな管の形成につながります。
The Müllerian duct and the Wolffian duct will have a very
ミュラー管とウォルフ管は、
very
非常に
important for the development of the urogenital system, male and
泌尿生殖器系、男性生殖器、
and
および
female. This is a section of the posterior parietal peritoneum in which we see
女性の発生にとって重要です。これは後方壁側腹膜の断面で、そこには
here what are called the cortical cords or what we can call the
ここでは皮質索と呼ばれるもの、または将来の精巣、生殖堤と呼ばれるものが見えます。
future testicles, the genital ridge.
将来の精巣、生殖堤。
Here, you have the Wolffian body with what is called the Wolffian duct,
そこには、ウォルフ体と、私たちがウォルフ管と呼ぶものがあります。
Wolffian duct, here, you see.
ウォルフ管が、ここにあるのが見えます。
And there, laterally, you have the appearance of what is called the Müllerian duct.
そして、その側方には、ミュラー管と呼ばれるものが出現しています。
In fact, in men, it doesn't develop that strongly.
実際、男性では、それはそれほど強く発達しません。
Why? Because it's not pushed that laterally.
なぜなら、それはそれほど側方に押し出されないからです。
It is said that the Wolffian duct differentiates into the vas deferens and by budding into
ウォルフ管は、男性では精管に分化し、芽生えによって尿管に分化すると言われています。
the ureter in men.
男性では尿管に分化します。
There is a connection with this canal that was created initially.
最初に作られたこの管とのつながりがあります。
which was the Wolffian duct, which will connect with the testicular area,
それはウォルフ管であり、発達中の精巣領域、
if you will, in development, with the tunica albuginea,
もしあなたが望むなら、白膜領域と接続し、
and it will make connections that will form the small canal here,
そして、それはここに小さな管を形成するつながりを作ります。
which is called the Wolffian duct, the epididymis.
ウォルフ管、精巣上体と呼ばれるものです。
Then here, we will have an important ligament,
そして、ここには重要な靭帯があります。
which is the gubernaculum testis ligament.
それは精巣導帯靭帯です。
And then, we see here that it will continue with the vas deferens
そして、ここから精管に続いて、
to continue, to form the seminal vesicle and the ejaculatory duct.
精嚢と射精管を形成するために続きます。
whereas the Müllerian duct here regresses but it will just leave a
一方、ミュラー管はここでは退化しますが、痕跡を残すだけです。
small ball here up
ここにある小さな球体
up there which is called the sessile hydatid which has no function to my knowledge which is a vestige
上にあるのは、私の知る限り機能を持たない痕跡であるハイドロアチル・セシルと呼ばれるものです。
it regresses on the other hand what is important is that it will give what is called the
それは退化しますが、重要なのは、それが私たちが呼ぶものになるということです。
prostatic utricle
前立腺小室
which later will still be enveloped by another endodermal tissue
それは後に別の内胚葉組織によってさらに包み込まれます。
to form this prostate
この前立腺を形成するために
which will be connected later to
それは後で接続されます
with the system of vas deferens, which themselves come from the Wolffian duct.
ウォルフ管から来る精管系と。
In women, it will form both the fallopian tubes and the uterus,
女性の場合、それは卵管と子宮の両方を形成し、
and in men, it will just form a part of their prostate.
男性の場合、それは前立腺の一部を形成するだけです。
But on the other hand, what is interesting is that everything is directed towards your
しかし、興味深いのは、すべてがあなたの方向に向かっていることです。
midline.
正中線。
At the level of the uterus, it organizes itself like that.
子宮のレベルでは、それはこのように組織されています。
However, on the testicular plane, you have a ligament.
しかし、睾丸の面では、靭帯があります。
gubernaculum which shortens and does not develop here and so the system will pull the
短縮する導帯はここでは発達せず、したがってシステムは
testicles
睾丸
will be held downwards if you will, you see, compared to the system that lengthens and so there
もしあなたが望むなら、伸びるシステムと比較して、それらは下向きに維持されます。したがって、
is like a downward force that is related to the development of the gonad so
性腺の発達に関連する下降力があります。したがって、
the gonad if
性腺はもし
you will, it is held from below but as it grows it goes like this by the differential
あなたが望むなら、それは下から維持されますが、それが成長するにつれて、それは速度によってこのように動きます。
growth
の
growth rates of the posterior part it will follow the development
後部の分化成長により、それは発達に従います。
and comes to be positioned downwards.
そして下方に移動します。
In the testicles, it will be the same thing,
睾丸でも同じことが起こります。
it will be the gubernaculum with the inguinal ligament
それは導帯と鼠径靭帯になります。
which will bring the system downwards.
システムを下方に導きます。
This means that it is suspended up to the diaphragmatic level initially,
それは、最初は横隔膜レベルまで吊り下げられていることを意味しますが、
but everything is pushed back initially by my hepatic movement.
しかし、すべては最初、私の肝臓の動きによって再び押し戻されます。
So this hepatic movement not only organizes the entire peritoneal cavity,
したがって、この肝臓の動きは、腹膜腔全体を組織するだけでなく、
but in a certain way, it will organize all your movement of urogenital development.
ある意味で、それはあなたの泌尿生殖器の発達の動き全体を組織するでしょう。
The importance of this liver, both in its metabolic function and in
この肝臓の重要性は、その代謝機能と
its embryonic function.
その胚性機能の両方において。
This small vestige here is a vestige of this.
ここにあるこの小さな痕跡は、これの痕跡です。
This is what is called the prostatic utricle which comes from the Müllerian duct.
これはミュラー管に由来する前立腺小室と呼ばれるものです。
Inside, it's epithelial tissue, urogenital tissue, that is
その中には、上皮組織、泌尿生殖器組織、つまり
-to-say endodermal.
内胚葉性組織があります。
And the prostate will develop from this tissue.
そして前立腺は、この組織から発達します。
This means that the prostatic utricle, therefore the core of the prostate, is
それは、前立腺小室、つまり前立腺の核心は、
is mesenchyme and the surrounding envelope, the capsule, says the prostate, is
間葉であり、その周りの被膜、つまり前立腺の被膜は、
is endoderm that comes from the urogenital sinus.
泌尿生殖器洞に由来する内胚葉であるということです。
That's where you had the cloaca, the allantois and the rectum
そこには総排出腔、尿膜管、直腸がありました。
behind again and with the meeting that leaves to form the bud.
さらにその後ろには、ブルジョワを形成するための出会いがあります。
ureteric bud to induce the definitive kidney which comes from the
尿管芽が、ウォルフ管から来る最終的な腎臓を誘導するために。
Wolffian duct.
ウォルフ管。
Compared to this testicle which was initially very high, with what we call
最初非常に高位にあったこの精巣に関して、いわゆる
the gubernaculum here, this testicular descent that occurs here,
ここにある導帯（gubernaculum）によって、この精巣下降がここで起こります。
this
この
ligament no longer develops and so by growth it pulls the
靭帯はそれ以上発達せず、成長によってシステムを引っ張ります。
system here
システムをここに
while the other ligament lengthens relatively compared
一方、もう一方の靭帯は、後方壁側腹膜に対して相対的に伸びます。
to the posterior parietal peritoneum.
後方壁側腹膜に対して。
We call it here the suspensory ligament of the ovary,
ここでは卵巣提靭帯と呼びますが、実際には
but in fact it's the ligament
実際には、それは
gonadal suspensory ligament
性腺提靭帯であり、
which is a ligament
それは靭帯です。
in relation to the diaphragm.
横隔膜と関係しています。
It has different names, suspensory ligament
それは様々な名前を持っています。提靭帯、
diaphragmatic or
横隔膜提靭帯、あるいは
testicular suspensory ligament
精巣提靭帯、
or ovarian suspensory ligament.
または卵巣提靭帯。
This attachment here
ここにあるこの付着部、
with the gubernaculum ligament
導帯靭帯との結合部が、
which comes to be placed on the inferior part
下部に位置し、そして様々な層が、
that I can't find anymore.
もう見つかりません。
by growth it causes this phenomenon there you
成長によってこの現象が引き起こされます。
see in fact it's a
実際、これは
global growth rate of this ligament which
この靭帯全体の成長速度であり、
seems to reduce but
縮小しているように見えますが、
it's everything else that grows, that's how you have the testicular descent
残りのすべてが成長しているのです。このようにして精巣下降が起こります。
testicular descent it was suspended by the suspensory ligament
精巣下降は、精巣提靭帯または
testicular or
精巣提靭帯または
diaphragmatic so that means that it is necessary to
横隔膜提靭帯によって吊り下げられていました。つまり、
re-examine up to the diaphragmatic level and more precisely at the duodeno-pancreatic junction.
横隔膜レベル、より正確には十二指腸膵臓の交差点まで見直す必要があります。
-pancreatic junction.
-膵臓の交差点まで見直す必要があります。